<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<event>
    <name>Analyze VM core</name>
    <name xml:lang="as">VM কেন্দ্ৰ বিশ্লেষণ কৰক</name>
    <name xml:lang="bg">Анализира VM средата</name>
    <name xml:lang="bn">VM core বিশ্লেষণ করুন</name>
    <name xml:lang="bn_IN">VM core বিশ্লেষণ করুন</name>
    <name xml:lang="cs">Analyzovat jádro VM</name>
    <name xml:lang="da">Analysér VM-kerne</name>
    <name xml:lang="de">VM-Core analysieren</name>
    <name xml:lang="en_GB">Analyse VM core</name>
    <name xml:lang="es">Analizar núcleo de VM</name>
    <name xml:lang="et">Analüüsi VM tuuma</name>
    <name xml:lang="fi">Analysoi VM-ydin</name>
    <name xml:lang="fr">Analyser le coeur VM</name>
    <name xml:lang="gu">VM કોરનું વિશ્ર્લેષણ કરો</name>
    <name xml:lang="hi">वी एम कोर का विश्लेषण करे </name>
    <name xml:lang="hu">VM mag elemzése</name>
    <name xml:lang="it">Analizza VM core</name>
    <name xml:lang="ja">仮想マシンのコアを分析</name>
    <name xml:lang="kn">VM ಕೋರ್ ಅನ್ನು ವಿಶ್ಲೇಷಿಸಿ</name>
    <name xml:lang="ko">VM 코어 분석 </name>
    <name xml:lang="lt">Analizuoti VM pagrindą</name>
    <name xml:lang="ml">വിഎം കോര്‍ നിരീക്ഷിയ്ക്കുക</name>
    <name xml:lang="mr">VM कोरचे विश्लेषण करा</name>
    <name xml:lang="nl">analyseer VM core</name>
    <name xml:lang="or">VM ମୂଖ୍ୟକୁ ବିଶ୍ଳେଷଣ କରନ୍ତୁ</name>
    <name xml:lang="pa">VM ਕੋਰ ਦੀ ਜਾਂਚ ਕਰੋ</name>
    <name xml:lang="pl">Analizuje plik vmcore</name>
    <name xml:lang="pt">Analisar núcleo VM</name>
    <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Analisa o VM core</name>
    <name xml:lang="ru">Диагностика отказа системы</name>
    <name xml:lang="sk">Analyzovať obsah jadra</name>
    <name xml:lang="sv">Analysera VM-kärna</name>
    <name xml:lang="ta">VM கோரை ஆராயவும்</name>
    <name xml:lang="te">VM కోర్ విశ్లేషించు</name>
    <name xml:lang="tr">VM çekirdeğini çözümle</name>
    <name xml:lang="uk">Проаналізувати ядро ВМ</name>
    <name xml:lang="zh_CN">分析 VM 核</name>
    <name xml:lang="zh_TW">分析 VM 核心</name>
    <description>Install kernel debuginfo packages, generate kernel log and oops message</description>
    <description xml:lang="as">কাৰনেল debuginfo পেকেইজসমূহ ইনস্টল কৰক, কাৰনেল লগ আৰু oops বাৰ্তা সৃজন কৰক</description>
    <description xml:lang="bg">Инсталира debuginfo пакети за ядрото, генерира журнал за ядрото и oops съобщение</description>
    <description xml:lang="bn">Kernel debuginfo প্যাকেজগুলি ইনস্টল করে, kernel লগ ও oops বার্তা প্রস্তুত করা হয়</description>
    <description xml:lang="bn_IN">Kernel debuginfo প্যাকেজগুলি ইনস্টল করে, kernel লগ ও oops বার্তা প্রস্তুত করা হয়</description>
    <description xml:lang="cs">Nainstalujte balíček kernel debuginfo a vygenerujte kernel log a oops zprávu</description>
    <description xml:lang="da">Installér kerne-debuginfo pakkerne, generér kernelog og oops-besked</description>
    <description xml:lang="de">Kernel-Debuginfo-Pakete installieren, Kernel-Protokoll und Kernelabsturz-Nachricht erzeugen</description>
    <description xml:lang="en_GB">Install kernel debuginfo packages, generate kernel log and oops message</description>
    <description xml:lang="es">Instalar paquetes de información de depuración, generar registro de kernel y mensaje oops</description>
    <description xml:lang="et">Paigalda tuuma silumisinfo pakid, genereeri tuuma logi ja uupsi teade</description>
    <description xml:lang="fi">Asenna debuginfo-paketit, luo ytimen loki ja oops-viesti</description>
    <description xml:lang="fr">Installe les paquetages debuginfo du noyau, génère le journal du noyau et les messages oops</description>
    <description xml:lang="gu">કર્નલ debuginfo પેકેજોને સ્થાપિત કરો, કર્નલ લૉગ અને oops સંદેશાને ઉત્પન્ન કરો</description>
    <description xml:lang="hi">कर्नेल डिबगइंफो संकुल को संस्थापित करें, कर्नेल लॉग और वूप्स संदेश उत्पन्न करें</description>
    <description xml:lang="hu">Telepítse a kernel debuginfo csomagokat, állítson elő kernel log-ot, és hibaüzeneteket.</description>
    <description xml:lang="it">Installa i pacchetti debuginfo del kernel, genera i messaggi oops ed i log del kernel</description>
    <description xml:lang="ja">カーネル debuginfo パッケージをインストールしてカーネルログと oops メッセージを生成します</description>
    <description xml:lang="kn">ಕರ್ನಲ್ debuginfo(s) ಅನ್ನು ಅನುಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸಿ, ಕರ್ನಲ್ ದಿನಚರಿಯನ್ನು ಮತ್ತು oops ಸಂದೇಶವನ್ನು ಉತ್ಪಾದಿಸಿ</description>
    <description xml:lang="ko">커널 debuginfo 패키지를 설치하고 커널 로그 및 oops 메세지를 생성합니다 </description>
    <description xml:lang="lt">Įdiegti branduolio derinimo informacijos paketus, generuoti branduolio žurnalą ir oops pranešimą</description>
    <description xml:lang="ml">കേര്‍ണല്‍ debuginfo പാക്കേജുകള്‍ ഇന്‍സ്റ്റോള്‍ ചെയ്യുക. കേര്‍ണല്‍ ലോഗും oops സന്ദേശവും ലഭ്യമാക്കുക</description>
    <description xml:lang="mr">कर्नल डिबगइंफो संकुल प्रतिष्ठापीत करा, कर्नल लॉग व ऊप्स् संदेश निर्माण करा</description>
    <description xml:lang="nl">Installeer kerneldebuginfo-pakketten, genereer kernellog en oops-boodschap</description>
    <description xml:lang="or">କର୍ଣ୍ଣଲ ତ୍ରୁଟି ନିବାରଣ ପ୍ୟାକେଜଗୁଡ଼ିକୁ ସ୍ଥାପନ କରନ୍ତୁ, କର୍ଣ୍ଣଲ ଲଗ ଏବଂ oops ସନ୍ଦେଶକୁ ସୃଷ୍ଟି କରନ୍ତୁ</description>
    <description xml:lang="pa">ਕਰਨਲ debuginfo ਪੈਕੇਜ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰੋ, ਕਰਨਲ ਲਾਗ ਅਤੇ oops ਸੁਨੇਹਾ ਬਣਾਓ</description>
    <description xml:lang="pl">Instaluje pakiety debuginfo jądra, tworzy dziennik jądra i komunikat oops</description>
    <description xml:lang="pt">Instala os pacotes debuginfo do kernel, gera o log do kernel e mensagens de oops</description>
    <description xml:lang="pt_BR">Instalar os pacotes do kernel debuginfo, gerar o log do kernel e mensagens do oops</description>
    <description xml:lang="ru">Установка пакетов для отладки ядра и создание журнала ошибок ядра</description>
    <description xml:lang="sk">Nainštalovať debuginfo balíčky jadra, vygenerovať protokol a oops správu</description>
    <description xml:lang="sv">Installera kärnans felsökningspaket, generera kärnlogg och oops-meddelanden</description>
    <description xml:lang="ta">கெர்னல் பிழைத்திருத்ததகவல் தொகுப்புகளை நிறுவவும், கெர்னல் பதிவு மற்றும் ஊப்ஸ் செய்தியை உருவாக்கவும்</description>
    <description xml:lang="te">కెర్నల్ డీబగ్‌యిన్ఫో ప్యాకేజీలను సంస్థాపించు, కెర్నల్ లాగ్ మరియు oops సందేశంను సృష్టించు</description>
    <description xml:lang="tr">kernel debuginfo paketlerini kur , kernel günlüğü ve oops mesajı üret</description>
    <description xml:lang="uk">Встановити пакунки діагностичних даних ядра, створити журнал дій ядра і повідомлень щодо помилок</description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_CN">安装内核 debuginfo 软件包，生成内核日志和 oops 信息</description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_TW">安裝內核 debuginfo 套件，產生內核紀錄與 oops 訊息</description>
    <long-description>Needs to install kernel debuginfo packages, which might take significant time, and take up disk space.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="as">কাৰনেল debuginfo পেকেইজসমূহ ইনস্টল কৰাৰ প্ৰয়োজন, যি বহু সময়, আৰু ডিস্ক স্থান লব পাৰে।</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="bg">Нуждае се от инсталиране на debuginfo пакети, което може да отнеме значително време и ще заеме дисково пространство.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="bn">Kernel debuginfo প্যাকেজগুলি ইনস্টল করা প্রয়োজন এবং এর জন্য বেশ কিছু পরিমাণ সময় ব্যয় হবে ও ডিস্কের অনেক স্থানও দখল করা হবে।</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="bn_IN">Kernel debuginfo প্যাকেজগুলি ইনস্টল করা প্রয়োজন এবং এর জন্য বেশ কিছু পরিমাণ সময় ব্যয় হবে ও ডিস্কের অনেক স্থানও দখল করা হবে।</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="cs">Je třeba nainstalovat ladící balíčky jádra, což může chvíli trvat a zabere část místa na pevném disku.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="da">Mangler at installere kerne debuginfo-pakker, kan tage ret lang tid og optage diskplads.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="de">Kernel-Debuginfo-Pakete müssen installiert werden, dies kann einige Zeit in Anspruch nehmen und benötigt Speicherplatz.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="en_GB">Needs to install kernel debuginfo packages, which might take significant time, and take up disk space.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="es">Es necesario instalar paquetes de información de depuración de kernel, los cuales pueden tomar un tiempo significativo y ocupar espacio de disco </long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="et">Peab paigaldama tuuma silumisinfo pakid, mis võib võtta märkmisväärselt aega ja kettaruumi.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="fi">Ytimen debuginfo-paketit on asennettava, tämä saattaa viedä paljon aikaa ja levytilaa</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="fr">Nécessite l'installation de paquetages debuginfo du noyau, celle-ci peut prendre un certain temps et occuper de l'espace disque.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="gu">કર્નલ debuginfo પેકેજોને સ્થાપિત કરવાની જરૂર છે, કે જે નોંધપાત્ર સમય લઇ શકે છે, અને ડિસ્ક જગ્યા લઇ શકે છે.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="hi">कर्नेल डिबगइंफो संकुल को संस्थापित करने की जरूरत, जो महत्वपूर्ण समय ले सकता है, और डिस्क स्पेस ले पाता है.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="hu">Szükséges a kernel debuginfo csomagok telepítése, ami elég sokáig eltarthat, és rengeteg tárhelyet emészthet fel.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="it">Necessita di una installazione dei pacchetti debuginfo del kernel, questo processo potrebbe richiedere molto tempo e spazio del disco.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ja">カーネル debuginfo パッケージをインストールする必要があります。 インストールにはかなりの時間がかかり、 またディスク領域も必要です。</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="kn">ಕರ್ನಲ್ ದೋಷನಿದಾನಮಾಹಿತಿ ಪ್ಯಾಕೇಜುಗಳ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿರುತ್ತದೆ, ಇದಕ್ಕೆ ಬಹಳ ಸಮಯ ಹಿಡಿಯಬಹುದು ಮತ್ತು ಡಿಸ್ಕಿನ ಜಾಗವೂ ಸಹ ಬಳಸಲ್ಪಡಬಹುದು.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ko">커널 debuginfo 패키지를 설치해야 합니다. 이는 다소 시간이 소요될 수 있으며 디스크 공간을 차지하게 됩니다. </long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="lt">Reikia įdiegti branduolio derinimo informacijos paketus, tai gali ilgai užtrukti ir užimti daug disko vietos.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ml">കേര്‍ണല്‍ debuginfo പാക്കേജുകള്‍ ഇന്‍സ്റ്റോള്‍ ചെയ്യേണ്ടതുണ്ടു്, ഇതു് വളരെ സമയവും ഡിസ്ക് സ്ഥലവും ഉപയോഗിയ്ക്കുന്നു.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="mr">कर्नल debuginfo संकुले प्रतिष्ठापीत करणे आवश्यक आहे, ज्यास लक्षणीय वेळ लागू शकतो, व डिस्क जागेचा वापर होऊ शकतो.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="nl">Kerneldebuginfo-pakketten moeten geïnstalleerd worden, dat kan behoorlijk wat tijd kosten en veel schijfruimte vergen.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="or">କର୍ଣ୍ଣଲ ତ୍ରୁଟିନିବାରଣ ପ୍ୟାକେଜଗୁଡ଼ିକୁ ସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଆବଶ୍ୟକ, ଯାହାକି ହୁଏତଃ କିଛି ସମୟ, ଏବଂ ଡିସ୍କ ସ୍ଥାନ ନେଇପାରେ।</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="pa">ਕਰਨਲ debuginfo ਪੈਕੇਜ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਲੋੜ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸਨੂੰ ਕੁਝ ਸਮਾਂ ਲੱਗ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਡਿਸਕ ਸਪੇਸ ਵੀ ਲੈ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ।</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="pl">Należy zainstalować pakiety debuginfo jądra, co może zająć dużo czasu i miejsca na dysku.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="pt">Obriga a instalar pacotes debuginfo do kernel, o que pode demorar algum tempo, e ocupa espaço em disco.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="pt_BR">Precisa instalar os pacotes do kernel debuginfo, que deve tomar bastante tempo, e tomar o espaço do disco.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ru">Требует установки пакетов debuginfo, что может занять значительное время и требует наличия дополнительного пространства.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="sk">Je potrebné nainštalovať debuginfo balíčky jadra, čo môže trvať značné množstvo času a zabrať diskový priestor.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="sv">Behöver installera paket med felsökningsinformation för kärnan, vilket kan ta en hel del tid, och använda diskutrymme.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="ta">கெர்னல் பிழைத்திருத்ததகவல் தொகுப்புகளை நிறுவ வேண்டும்,  போதுமான நேரம், மற்றும் வட்டு இடத்தை எடுத்தலை செய்கிறது.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="te">కెర్నల్ డీబగ్‌యిన్ఫో ప్యాకేజీలను సంస్థాపించవలసివుంది, యిది కొంత సమయం తీసుకొనవచ్చును, మరియు డిస్కు జాగాను కూడా తీసుకొనును.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="uk">Потребує встановлення пакунків діагностичних даних ядра, на що може знадобитися доволі багато часу і місця на диску.</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="zh_CN">需要安装内核 debuginfo 软件包，安装该软件包需要很长时间，并占用磁盘空间。</long-description>
    <long-description xml:lang="zh_TW">需要安裝內核 debuginfo 套件，並且可能會花上一段長時間以及消耗磁碟空間。</long-description>
    <creates-items>backtrace</creates-items>
    <gui-review-elements>no</gui-review-elements>
</event>